babevideo.co.uk 2019-05-06

# Babe Video

(A) Introduction

Babe Video is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website members and visitors. This policy sets out how we store and use your personal information.

The policy applies to those who have registered an account with us and to guests who visit and view the site but who have not completed an account registration. By using this website you expressly agree to this privacy policy and to the data privacy practices described here. If you do not agree you should not use our website.

The policy is divided into the following sections.

(B) Age & Location

You must be at least 18 years old to use this website, www.babevideo.co.uk.

If you are at least 18 years of age, we welcome you to our website which is primarily concerned with adult television channels broadcast in the UK and Ireland. The site is primarily intended to be viewed by people living in those countries, although we are fully aware and appreciate that we have visitors from all over the world.

If you are not viewing this site in the UK or Ireland, you are still very welcome to use our site, as we value all our vistors from all jurisdictions. However, as this an adult entertainment site it is your own responsibility to check the laws and ordinances of the country and the state you are accessing the site from to ensure that you are not in violation of any law by entering or viewing this website.

As our websites are not intended for those under 18 we do not knowingly collect data relating to anyone of that age.

If we become aware or have good reason to believe that a member of the site is under the age of 18 the account in question will be closed immediately. If you suspect that someone here is underage please make this known to us as soon as possible.

If you believe a child or yours under the age of 18 has entered personal information here, please contact us to have the data removed and terminate the child's account.

We recommend that parents and guardians supervise their children while they are online. There are various control tools available for online activities that we advise parents to utilise in order to create a child-friendly online environment for their children.

(C) Cookies

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

Like most websites, this website uses cookies and all visitors to the site are advised of our use of cookies when first arriving on the website.

The site uses two types of cookies, session cookies and persistent cookies. It uses persistent cookies to identify you when you visit and to distinguish you as a website visitor from other users of our website. It uses session cookies to open and close a session (for example, to allow login to and logout of the site).

Persistent cookies are stored on your computer until deleted, but session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser.

The site does not use any cookies for the purpose of analytics, the tracking and reporting of website traffic or website performance, such as those used by Google Analytics and similar tools.

Most browsers allow you to deny/disable cookies very easily, but blocking all cookies in this way will make it impossible for site members to login to their accounts.

For more information on how the site uses cookies please refer to our Cookies Policy.

(D) Data Collection

Babe Video collects both personal data and aggregated data.

Personal data, or personal information, refers to any information about an individual from which that person could be identified.

On this website we collect and store the following kinds of personal information:

(1) the email address that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us. You can access the email address we hold for you in your account management options and amend it at any time.

(2) information about your visits to and use of the site, such as your IP address including therefore your internet service provider and your geographical location, your browser type and version, your computer operating system, your referral source, the length of your visit, your page views and your forum navigation.

(3) any other information that you choose to provide, such as personal information revealed through your username, avatar, profile, media uploads, site comments, private messages and emails. You must have a username to register an account, but you are not required to enter any profile details in order to use the site.

Aggregated data refers to statistical data which is used to better understand how our visitors are using the site and to improve site performance. On many websites aggregated data is derived from personal data, but the aggregated data we collect on this site is not derived from personal data and could not be used to reveal your identity, either directly or indirectly.

(E) Data Use

Information that we collect from you is stored and processed in the USA which is the country in which the site is located. You expressly agree to this.

We may use the personal information we collect from you to:

(1) administer the site, which means sending you newsletters, service messages and policy updates from the site admin.

(2) improve your user experience by personalising the site.

(3) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you regarding the use or operation of the site.

If you prefer not to have your personal data used as described above you should not join the site. You are always welcome to view the site as a guest and are not obliged to register as a member. Most of our site visitors are guests and not members.

If you are registered as a member, please be aware that your username and any additional content you provide through your member profile, your media uploads or comments that you contribute to the site are fully visible not only to other members but to anyone visiting the site as a guest.

We will not under any circumstances provide your email address to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing or for any other commercial purpose.

(F) Site Comments

Please note that if you post personal information in comments you contribute to the site you do so at your own risk, including the risk of abandoning any privacy rights you had in such information (as we are obviously unable to prevent the use or misuse of such information by others once you have published it on the worldwide web). 

However, please note that personal information posted in site comments may be regarded as inappropriate and removed by site staff. In particular any email addresses and telephone numbers which are posted in comments are likely to be removed.

Regarding any comments you contribute here, you agree to grant to the site a non-exclusive, royalty-free, worldwide, perpetual license to have the comments visible on the site and to reproduce, distribute, transmit and create derivative works of them, without any right of rescission whatsoever. This means that you cannot revoke permission for UK Babe Channels to publish and to allow others to have derivative rights to content once you have yourself made it public, and you should be aware that in any event UK Babe Channels loses direct control over such content when it is published on the open internet. You also agree that you shall have no recourse against the site for any alleged or actual infringement or misappropriation of any proprietary right in your comments.

If a comment made by another member includes information that could be considered invasive of your privacy it is likely to be removed. If not you are free to contact us and ask for the relevant material to be removed. We take no responsibility for the content of messages posted, other than to remove them from the site where considered appropriate, and we cannot be held liable for the content of any messages posted.

Comments may contain links to other websites. We have no control over such third party websites and have no responsibility for their privacy policies or their practices.

(G) Data Security

Babe Video is committed to protecting your privacy by storing your data securely and by regularly testing our security measures. We have procedures in place to deal with any suspected data security breach.

All the data you provide us with is stored securely without any exceptions and we will take all reasonable technical and operational measures to prevent the disclosure of your registration email address and any other email address that you subsequently use. 

Unfortunately, no transmission of data over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, and despite our efforts, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and have no responsibility or liability for the security of information transmitted via the internet, including any act of hacking in which your data is compromised.

You play an important role in keeping your information secure, as you are responsible for choosing your password and keeping it confidential. Please use a strong password in order to protect your account and guard it carefully. You can change your password at any time in your account management options.

Please note that if your account is hacked the hacker will have access to your stored email address. The importance of account security cannot be over-emphasised, as with access to your account the hacker will also be able to impersonate you on the site. Again, you can change your password at any time in your account management options .

If you forget your password, you can use the "lost password" option, which requires you to submit your email address in order to have a new password generated. Please note that if your registered email address is no longer valid you will not be able to reset your password in this way.

(H) Data Disclosure

If you take part in a site competition and win a prize, it may be necessary to provide some personal information of yours to the sponsor of the competition in order that the prize can be awarded to you. This would depend on your express consent being sought and given at the time.

In addition we may disclose information about you to to the extent that we are required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings or to provide the information to anyone who we believe may successfully apply to a court for the disclosure of the information.

We will not under any circumstances provide any of your personal information to a third party for the purpose of direct marketing or for any other commercial purpose.

If you disclose personal information yourself by posting it in comments you contribute to the site you do so at your own risk, as mentioned in section (F) above.

Personal information may also be passed to other members by using the site's private message system. As private messages are private they are not visible to the public or to members of the site other than those a specific message was sent to. 

If you disclose personal information about yourself by private message you do so at your own risk, as you are dependent upon the recipient respecting your privacy. 

All information that we hold is stored and processed in the USA which is the country in which the site is located. We will not transfer any of your personal information to any other country without your express consent being sought and given at the time. 

(I) Data Control

The control and processing of personal data is governed by the General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (GDPR).

The data controller for this website is the site owner, UK Babe Channels. There are no other parties involved.

The GDPR requires us to always have a lawful basis for the collection and processing of your personal information. The lawful basis for the information we collect here is that the processing is necessary for the legitimate interests pursued by the data controller, UK Babe Channels, which is authorised by GDPR article 6(1)(f).

In addition we may process your personal information if it is necessary to comply with a legal obligation or to defend a legal claim, which is authorised by GDPR article 6(1)(c), or if processing that data is necessary to protect someone, which is authorised by GDPR article 6(1)(d).

As the party solely responsible for your personal data and in order to carry out these responsibilities as effectively as possible we have appointed a data privacy manager. Our data privacy manger can be contacted by emailing him at dataprivacy@babechannels.co.uk

If contacting us, kindly state to which website your query refers, as our data privacy manager is responsible for privacy policy on all UK Babe Channels websites. 

We will hold your personal data securely for as long as you are registered as a member of the site and usually for a further 3 years following cessation of membership. We do not keep any personal information in document form and any data that we retain is stored in databases.

(J) Your Rights

The General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (GDPR) provides you with the following legal rights over the storing and processing of your your personal information.

To ask for a copy of the personal information we hold about you.  
To ask for a copy of your personal data in a machine-readable format.  
To know what we are doing with your information and why we are doing it.  
To ask us to correct any mistakes in the information we hold about you.  
To object to your personal data being used for direct marketing purposes.  
To object to your data being used in a way which infringes your human rights.  
To ask for your personal data to be deleted if we don't require it any longer.  
To ask us to limit or restrict the of processing of your personal data.  
To withdraw your consent at any time to the processing of your data.

If you have registered an online account with us and would like to update the information you have provided to us, you can access your account via your account management options to view and make changes or corrections to your information.

Please note that these rights don't apply to personal information that you have made public yourself in comments you have posted on the site.

(K) Requests

We will comply with any requests to exercise your rights in accordance with the GDPR. Please note, however, that there are a number of legal limitations to these rights, and there may be circumstances where we are not able to comply with your request. If we are unable to comply with a request we will notify you of the specific legal reasons for this or demonstrate to you that we have compelling legitimate grounds which override your rights.

If you exercise your right to restrict the of processing of your personal information, where we are are using it in a specific way you wish to discontinue, it will be understood that you do not wish your data to be further processed in that way, but that you do want us to continue to store it.

If you exercise your right to ask for your personal information to be deleted, where you feel that we do not require it any longer, we will proceed to delete that information immediately unless there are other interests in that information which we hold to outweigh your right to deletion, such as legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings.

For further information on privacy law you can consult the GDPR and you can also refer to the guidance from the UK Information Commissioner's Office (ICO) on your privacy rights under GDPR and the circumstances in which those rights apply.

The ICO is the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues. Their website can be accessed at www.ico.org.uk and concerns may be reported at https://ico.org.uk/concerns.

(L) Contact

If you have a query on any aspect of this privacy policy or the handling of your personal information, including any requests to exercise your rights under GDPR, please contact our data privacy manager by emailing him at dataprivacy@babechannels.co.uk

If contacting us, kindly state to which website your query refers, as our data privacy manager is responsible for privacy policy on all UK Babe Channels websites. 

The forum contains many links to other websites, including advertising banners. We have no control over such third party websites and have no responsibility for their privacy policies or their practices. However, we value any feedback about these third party sites and you are welcome to contact us with information or your views about any site that we link to (including if a specific link does not work).

Our policies and procedures are continually under review and for that reason we may update this privacy policy at any time by posting a new version on the site. We may make small, inconsequential changes to this policy with or without notice to you, so you may want to check this page from time to time to ensure you're happy with any changes which may have been made. Substantive changes to this policy may be sent to anyone who submits an email request to the data privacy manager.

By using this website you expressly agree to this privacy policy and to the data privacy practices described here. If you do not agree you should not use our website.

This privacy policy was last updated on 16 December 2018.
